All right, in this section, I'm going to explain to you step five of the breath stroke.
Now, this is going to be your upper body that you're going to use.
What you're going to want to do is your hands are going to want to be not open-handed; you're going to want them actually closed, and in a prayer position.
And you're going to be like this right in the center of your chest, so not in the lower part of your chest, and not up here, just right on the center.
So again, closed hands; no open gaps, right; prayer position, thumbs in like this, and then you're just aiming like in the chest.
So, you're going to be like this when you're doing breath stroke, to start off, in prayer position.
And that's step five when you're beginning the breath stroke.
In this section of the breath stroke it's a continuation of step five, and it's going to be the way you're going to place your hands.
So again, remember, no open hands, Make sure that they're closed like prayer position, and it's close to the chest, okay?
So, when you start off doing breath stroke, I showed you how to do your legs, and you want to make sure that your arms are like this under the water.
So when you're doing it, it's going to be just like this, okay?
So you're in prayer position.
This is your starting point, right here.
Not open hands, not out like this; just really close to the body; tight, in prayer position.